- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
我煮了咖啡  低咖咖啡
I made coffee. It's half-caf.
哦  太好了  谢谢
Oh, great. Thanks.
你写完英语试卷了吗
You get that, uh, English paper done?
- 写完了  - 哦 很好
- Uh-huh. - Oh, good, good.
我昨天跟你的社会工作者聊了聊
I talked to your social worker yesterday
希望我能继续领养你
about moving this adoption along.
- 是吗  - 是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
我们这周得跟她见几次面
We're gonna have to meet with her a couple times this week.
- 但是我之前跟她谈过了啊  - 我知道
- But I just talked to her. - I know.
我想 可能  她可能想看看我们相处的怎么样
I think, uh... I think she just wants to see how... how we're doing.
那罗伊呢
What about Roy?
我会找他谈的
I'll talk to Roy.
谢谢你  伯顿
Thanks, Burton.
- 别客气
- Yeah.
- 拜拜  - 好的  晚点见
- See you. - Okay. Later.
你们来了  进来吧  很抱歉
Here you go. Come on in. Sorry about that.
有点小意外
A little surprise going here.
把东西都拿到楼上吧
Everything goes upstairs.
你好  直接上去就行
How are you? Go ahead.
先生  不把它拿走的话其它东西放不进去
Sir, we can't fit this in until that's out of here.
哦  让我  先把抽屉清空一下
Oh, let me... empty these drawers.
这样会容易拿一点
It'll be a little easier to move it.
第三季  第十六集
法外真情
翻译   大淘子
校对  油 球
特效  转轮 枪
- 去几楼  - 呃 去法律服务部
- What floor? - Uh, Legal Services.
嗯  我就去那
Ah, that's where I'm going.
需要帮忙吗
You need some help?
不  不用了  我自己可以解决  没问题
No, no. I got it. No problem.
能帮点忙吗
A little help?
所有人都听我说
Everybody listen up!
我这有五千份竞选传单
I got five thousand campaign flyers!
请大家都拿一些  分发出去
Please, everybody... take some and disseminate them
走到哪  发到哪
anywhere and everywhere you go.
艾米莉·伯恩斯利来找路易莎·阿彻
Emily Bernsley for Louisa Archer.
大家都加把劲  还有两周就到选举日了
Come on, people! Only two weeks till Election Day!
嘿  劳瑞
Hey, Laurie.
市议会的吗
City Council?
是的  我是一个独立运营者
Yeah. I'm running as an Independent.
给我拿几张吧
I'll take a few.
谢谢
Thank you.
劳瑞  菲利普最近怎么样
Laurie, what's going on with Philip?
菲利普的养母不想要他
Phillip's foster mother doesn't want him.
我以为是奥罗克一家收养了他
I thought the O'Rourkes were adopting him.
- 他们刚刚有一个小女儿  - 是的
- They just had a baby girl. - Right.
这个孩子上周受伤了  头上缝了八针
The baby was injured last month. She had eight stitches in her head.
怎么回事
What happened?
婴儿座椅从阳台上掉下来了  孩子那时候正坐在里面
The infant seat fell off the counter. The baby was in it.
- 他们怪菲利普吗  - 那时候并没有
- They blame Philip? - Not then.
但是昨天奥罗克太太说菲利普在吓唬小宝宝
But yesterday Mrs. O'Rourke claimed that Philip was threatening the baby.
- 怎么吓的  - 没说
- How? - Didn't say.
她就打电话过来让我们把他接走
She just called and told us to pick him up.
- 艾米丽吗  - 是的
- Emily? - Yes.
我是路易莎·阿切尔·露露
I'm Louisa Archer. Lulu.
- 你好  - 你好
- Hi. - Hi.
你是伯恩斯利法官的女儿  对吧
You're Judge Bernsley's daughter, right?
是的
Right.
你能来志愿服务真的是太好了
It's really nice of you to volunteer like this.
我在法学院曾选修过关于儿童权益的课程
I took a course on children's rights in law school.
那太好了
Well, this looks great.
嗯  那你什么时候可以正式开始呢
Uh... when can you start?
我刚结束一个案子  所以现在就有时间
I just finished a case, so I'm free right now.
哦  好的
Oh. Okay.
露露  你拿传单了吗
Lulu? Did you get any flyers?
- 什么  - 我的竞选传单
- What? - My campaign flyers.
如果可以的话  多拿点  帮我发一发
lf you could, take a bunch and spread 'em around.
- 又见面了 - 嗨
- Hello again. - Hi.
桑德拉  别急着走
Sandra? Not so fast.
拿点传单
Take some flyers.
菲利普  你有吓唬那个小孩吗
Philip, did you threaten the baby?
法林先生  我没有对孩子做任何事情
I didn't do anything to the baby, Mr. Fallin.
你们打算怎么处置我
What's gonna happen to me?
呃  你知道的  劳瑞会尽量给你找一个新家
Uh... you know, um, Laurie will try to find you a new fam--
我不能待在奥罗克家了吗
I can't stay with the O'Rourkes?
现在不能了
Not right now.
我只是去看了看宝宝
I just looked at the baby
之后想亲一下她
and went to give her a kiss.
安妮就开始冲我大喊  让我滚开
Annie starts yelling at me and telling me to keep away
说我会伤到宝宝
and that I was gonna hurt her.
但是我没想伤害她
I wasn't gonna hurt her.
你还记得玩具都在哪吗
You remember where the toys are?
可以先出去玩一会吗
You mind just going out and playing for a little bit?
好的
Okay.
让我和劳瑞聊一会
While Laurie and I talk?
谢谢
Thank you.
别客气
All right.
所以  呃  当那个孩子受伤的时候
So, uh, when the baby was injured,
奥罗克太太有说看见他把孩子推下阳台吗
did Mrs. O'Rourke say that she saw him push her off the counter?
并没有  他那时在她转身看不见的地方
No. He was in the area, she turned around,
- 之后她就看见  - 好吧
- the next thing she knew... - Right.
我所知道的就是奥罗克一家不想再收养菲利普了
All I know is the O'Rourkes don't want Philip anymore.
是的
Yeah.
- 嘿
- Hey.
快上车
Come on. Get in.
伯顿  怎么了
Burton. What?
你问什么不告诉我这些事
Why didn't you tell me about these?
你不让我参加青少年匹兹堡小姐的选拔
You didn't let me try out for Miss Teen Pittsburgh.
因为我想让你专注于你的学业
Because I wanted you to focus on your studies.
我可以获胜的
I could've won.
宝贝  成为青少年匹兹堡小姐并能帮助你通过数学考试
Honey, being Miss Teen Pittsburgh is not gonna help you pass math.
我两个都能做好的  模特和学业
I can do both. Modeling and school.
至少现在  我希望你能专心学习
For right now, I want you to focus on your school work.
而且我打算跟这个摄影师聊聊
And I want to talk to that photographer.
- 为什么  - 因为我是你的监护人
- Why? - Because I'm your guardian.
因为我需要知道关于你的一切
Because I have to know everything you do.
一切
Everything.
所以  他叫什么名字
Now what's his name?
马尔科姆·里维斯
Malcolm Reeves.
他的影棚在哪里
Where's his studio?
在北区  爱丽丝大街
On the North Side. Alice Street.
马尔科姆跟许多模特和演员一起工作
Malcolm works with lots of models and actors.
他甚至为百货公司做陈列
And he even does layouts for department stores.
亲爱的  就好好做你的作业可以吗  我一会就回来
Honey, just do your homework, all right? I'll be back in a little while.
伯顿
Burton.
对不起
I'm sorry.
宝宝有绞痛
The baby has colic.
我一晚上大概睡了两个小时
I get... I get, like, two hours of sleep a night.
然后她就是  一直一直哭
And, uh, she just cries and cries and cries.
所以之后  法林先生  你知道的  我并不是超人
And then, you know, l... I am not superhuman, Mr. Fallin.
好吗  我不能一边照顾希瑟  一边成为菲利普的好妈妈
Okay? I can't look after Heather and be a good mom to Philip as well.
我不能这样  这对他也不公平  对我  对我也不公平
I can't do that. It's not fair to him. It's... it's not fair to me.
之后菲利普就做了这样的事情
And then Philip does something like that.
你确定菲利普是故意伤害孩子的吗
You're certain that Philip hurt the baby intentionally?
安全座椅自己又不能从台子上跳下去
The infant seat didn't just jump off the counter.
好吧
Okay.
而且他还做了个别的事情  你知道吗
And he does other things. You know?
他发出了  他发出了那些奇怪的声音
He makes... he makes these strange noises.
而且他  他  他总是这样盯着宝宝看
And he... he's... he's always Iooking at her with this look...
就好像  我不知道  就好像  他打算做什么坏事
like, I don't know, like he's... he's ready to do something evil.
而且她总是  总是哭  让我没法好好睡觉
And she's always... she's always crying and I can't sleep.
嗨
Hi.
抱歉  我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
奥罗克先生
Mr. O'Rourke?
- 来很久了吗  - 没有
- Been here long? - No.
我实在是讨厌发生这样的事情
I hate like hell that this is happening.
你们都应该知道的  呃  菲利普的档案里有这样的一个污点
You both understand that, uh... a mark like this on Philip's report
会使他以后很难
is gonna make it very difficult to...
你知道他生父曾经虐待他
You do know that his biological father abused him.
你也知道这意味着什么
You know what that means.
那他在你们家生活了两年  现在你才意识到他
So he's been living in your home for two years, and now you realize he's...
希瑟才是我的孩子  明白吗
Heather is my child. Okay?
我生了她  她是我的
l... I carried her. She's mine.
我没法跟你解释这是什么感觉
I can't explain to you what it's like to be...
要一直担心我的孩子  我
to be worried about your baby
all the time. l...
我实在没法跟你解释
I can't explain it to you.
我得去看希瑟了
I have to get Heather.
我没办法改变她的主意
I can't change her mind.
她一直说他是危险的
She keeps saying he's dangerous.
你也这样想吗
Do you think he is?
我不知道
I don't know.
我的意思是  大部分时候  他是一个可爱的孩子
I mean, most of the time, he is the sweetest kid.
是的  是的
Right, right.
肯定发生了些什么
There's definitely something going on
在他和我的妻子和希瑟之间
between he and my wife and Heather, though.
每次我离开家  好像一切都不正常了
Every time I leave the house, it's like everything just goes crazy.
我  我会告诉法官
l... I'll-- I'll let the judge know.
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
罗伊说他可以在同意书上签字
Roy said he could sign the consent forms.
是吗  但是他没权利
Yeah? Well, he can't.
我才是她的合法监护人
I'm her legal guardian.
我以为罗伊是香农的爸爸
I thought Roy was Shannon's dad.
是的  他的确是  但是一直是我在照顾她  所以
Yes, he is but I take care of her, so...
呃  我们该换衣服了
Uh... should we get changed?
好的  我马上过去
Yeah. I'll be with you in a minute.
这是个问题吗
ls this gonna be a problem?
你先告诉我你们都在这做了什么
Not if you tell me everything that's going on here.
先生  只是拍一些照片
Just pictures, sir.
香农想成为一名模特
Shannon wants to be a model.
我们就在这拍了一些照片
We were just taking some pictures.
给我看一下照片
I want to see those pictures.
好啊  可以
Fine. Okay.
好啦  就是这些
Okay. Here we go.
事实上  有些照片真的很好看
Actually, some of those are pretty good.
这并不是全部  还有一些穿泳装的
This isn't all of them. There's some in a bathing suit.
亲爱的  我应该穿哪件  还是什么都不穿
Sweetie? Shall I wear this, this, or nothing?
就  穿那件红色的吧
Just... wear the red one.
好的
Okay.
先生  这只是赚钱的一种方式
Sir, this is just a way to pay the rent.
给我所有的照片和底片
I want all the pictures and all the negatives.
马上
Now.
嘿
Hey.
劳瑞来了  呃  来跟我们聊聊
Laurie's here to, uh... interview us.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我的意思是  我把你做的一切都毁了
I mean, you did all this, and then... I ruined it.
哦  没事
Oh... well...
你跟马尔科姆聊过了吗
Did you talk to Malcolm?
哦  宝贝  我并不想你再过去了
Oh, honey, I don't, uh, I don't want you going over there again.
他做各种各样的事情  乐队  模特  艺术品
He does all sorts of things. Bands, models, art stuff.
他说这样我也许可以开始模特生涯
He says I can maybe have a career doing this.
香农  不许再去了  听明白了吗
Shannon, don't ever go over there again. Do you understand?
为什么不能去
Why not?
你不应该去
It's not appropriate.
但是马尔科姆说我很优秀
But Malcolm says I'm really good.
香农
Shannon.
我只是
I just...
我只是想有一些擅长的事
I just want to be good at something.
好吧
Fine.
如果你不是让我去  那我就不去了
lf you don't want me going, I won't go.
很好
Good.
过来吧  她在等着了
Now come on down. She's waiting.
尼克
Nick.
他们写错了我的名字
They misspelled my name.
我的名字被写错了
My name is misspelled.
- 哪呢  - 在底下
- Where? - On the bottom.
看到了吗  写着  由马斯特森支付给市议会
See? Where it says ''Paid for by Mastersin for City Council.''
马斯特森  S-l-N
Master-sin. S-l-N.
呃  不好意思  我得先走了
Uh, I'm sorry, I gotta go.
哦  尼克
Oh, Nick.
呃  尼克·法林  这位是艾米丽·伯恩斯利
Uh, Nick·Fallin, this is Emily·Bernsley.
- 哦  你是伯恩斯利法官的女儿  - 是的
- Oh, you're Judge Bernsley's daughter. - Right.
- 很高兴认识你  - 艾米丽在 Kirk & McGee律师事务所工作
- Nice to meet you. - Emily works for Kirk & McGee.
我知道
I know.
你是不是那个不在自己父亲公司工作的人
Aren't you the guy who left your dad's firm
然后过来我们公司工作
to come over and run our corporate department?
就是我
That's right.
哦  那为什么要这样做呢
Yeah, what happened with that?
呃  其实
Uh, well...
艾米丽昨天接了克拉莫德的案子
Emily took over the Cramord case yesterday,
而且已经给他找了一个寄养家庭
and she already found him a foster home.
太好了
Fantastic.
她需要跟你共用一间办公室
She's gonna need to share your office.
很好
Even better.
别介意  我们实在没有地方了
You won't really overlap. We just don't have any space, so...
失陪一下
Excuse me.
奥罗克先生
Mr. O'Rourke.
法林先生
Mr. Fallin.
我带来了菲利普的手套和运动衫
I've got Philip's mitt and his sweatshirt.
好的  谢谢
Right. Thanks.
所以今天开庭怎么样
So what happened in court today?
法官下令商讨
The judge ordered counseling.
那菲利普会去哪
And where's Philip gonna go?
福利院
The shelter.
有没有可能给他找一个新家呢
What are the chances of finding him a new family?
不太可能  至少现在不行
It's not good. Not now.
好吧
Right.
那商讨呢  现在就开始吗
And the counseling, it starts immediately?
是的
That's right.
- 那他们能帮助他吗  - 嗯  他们会尽力的
- And they can help him? - Well, they'll do the best they can.
好的
Okay.
替我跟他打个招呼  可以吗
Tell him I said hello, all right?
当然
Sure.
嘿  法林先生
Hey, Mr. Fallin.
什么风把你吹来了
What brings you over to my neck of the woods?
香农
Shannon.
罗伊  你不能签署香农的同意书
Roy, you can't sign consent forms for Shannon.
- 你在说什么  - 关于模特的
- What are you talking about? - Modeling.
那个影棚  他们会拍一些女人的裸照
That studio... they take photos of naked women.
你在说什么  裸照
What are you talking about... naked women?
你不是她的监护人
You're not her guardian.
没有我的允许  你甚至不能带她去公园走走
You can't even take her to the park without my permission.
好吧  你听着  我不知道什么裸照的事
Well, listen, I don't know anything about naked women.
我所知道的就是你不允许香农做她想做的事
All I know is you don't let Shannon do things she's good at.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
香农过来跟我说  她说你不让他参加选美
Shannon comes to me, and she says you won't let her do some pageants.
她说你一直逼着她学一些她不擅长的课程
She says you keep making her take classes she's not good at.
她总觉得自己什么都做不好
Says she feels stupid all the time.
而且  她想成为一个模特  我不会成为扼杀她梦想的人
So she's got a dream to model. I'm not gonna be the guy who kills it.
罗伊  我觉得我们应该再谈一谈
Roy, I think you and l better have another little talk
关于收养的问题  好吗
about finalizing this adoption, okay?
好吧  嘿  我有工作了  我在镇子安定下来了
Well, hey, I got a job. I've been here in town.
我一周看香农一次  我在做我应该做的事情
I see Shannon once a week. I'm doing what I'm supposed to do.
我才是她的爸爸  不是你
I'm her dad, man, not you.
你在影响我  你知道吗
You're screwing me, you know that?
这就是香农想要的
This is what Shannon wants.
这并不是她跟我说的
Well, that's not what she says to me.
事实上  这是她跟社会服务部说的
Well, that's what she told Social Services.
记录上都有的
That's on the record.
如果你再逼着她的话  她会在法庭上再说出来的
She'll say it again in a court of law if you make her do it.
你就同意收养就可以了
Just agree to the adoption.
你会有探视权
I'll give you visitation rights.
一万
Ten thousand.
什么
What?
一万美金  你想怎么样就怎么样
Ten thousand... I'll agree to whatever you want.
哦  罗伊
Oh, Roy.
嘿  劳瑞
Hey, Laurie.
- 伯顿  很高兴见到你  - 最近怎么样
- Burton. Nice to see you. - How are you?
- 还不错  谢谢  - 进来吧
- Fine, thanks. - Come on in.
谢谢
Thanks.
请坐
Have a seat there.
- 最近怎么样啊  - 还好  你呢
- How've you been? - Okay. And you?
还可以  谢谢
Good. Thank you.
那
So...
你知道我今早开了一个会
You know I had a meeting this morning
和瑟蒙德学院的校长
with the Headmistress at the Thurmond Academy.
海登太太  是的  她是一个  一个很了不起的女士
Mrs. Hayden, yeah. She's a... she's a terrific lady.
我希望你能了解香农在学校都在做什么
I assume you know how Shannon's been doing in school.
哦  是的 是的  我们在努力学习了
Oh, yeah, yeah. Yeah, we're working on that.
我  呃  给她请了一个家教  而且我也每天给她检查作业
l, uh, hired a tutor and I check her homework every night,
而且  我觉得  她也在进步
and I think, uh... I think she's improving.
海登太太并不认为香农拥有在瑟蒙德取得成功才能
Mrs. Hayden doesn't think Shannon has the skills she needs to succeed at Thurmond.
呃  这也是我们一直努力的原因
Uh... that's what we're working on.
她说她应该在五年级  不是八年级
She says she should be in the fifth grade, not the eighth grade.
哦  这太荒谬了
Oh, that's ridiculous.
伯顿  他们已经建议香农转校了
Burton, they're recommending that Shannon be placed in another school,
专区一个能满足她特殊需求的学校
a school that can meet her special needs.
特殊需求
Special needs?
她只是  她只是还没有准备好去你们让她去的学校
It's just that she's... not prepared for the school you've placed her in.
只是这样  伯顿
That's all, Burton.
嗨  伯顿
Hi, Burton.
嗨  亲爱的
Hi, honey.
罗伊就是过来打个招呼
Roy just came over to say hi.
哦  好的  去车里等我可以吗
Yeah. Right. Go wait in the car, okay?
- 去吧  去吧  - 拜拜
- Go ahead. Go on. - I'll see you soon.
拜
Bye.
这就是我想跟你说的
This is exactly what I'm talking about.
我不能来看我自己的女儿吗
I'm not allowed to see my own daughter?
没我的允许就不行
Not without my permission.
我就是跟她说清楚整件事
I was just talking to her about this whole thing.
看看她想怎样
Seeing what she wanted.
我的意思是  法林先生
I mean, Mr. Fallin...
听着  你是对的
Hey, you're right.
她想跟你在一起
She wants to be with you.
听着  我今天跟劳瑞·索尔特和海登太太谈过了
Listen, I talked to Laurie Solt and Mrs. Hayden today...
而且  呃  我们觉得瑟蒙德也许并不是一个适合你的学校
and, uh, we're thinking maybe Thurmond is not exactly the right school for you.
那我能回到我之前的学校吗
I can go back to my old school, then?
不  不行  我们正在想着去新边界
No, no. We're thinking about New Borders.
- 什么  - 新边界
- What? - New Borders.
那是一所弱智学校
That's a school for retards.
不  并不是   事实上  这是一个还不错的学校
No it's not. Actually, it's a pretty good school.
就是一个弱智学校
It's a school for retards.
宝贝  我  我知道今年对于你来说是非常艰难的一年
Honey... l, uh... I know this has been a tough year for you...
所有的改变和周围的一切
all the changes and everything,
但是  要不你就去试一两个学期
but... why don't you just try this for a semester or two?
之后我们再定下一步该做什么
Then we'll figure out what to do.
把我送回原来的学校吧  我不会去那的
Just send me back to my old school, then. I'm not going there.
好吧  我之后再跟你说  晚点我们再聊这件事
All right, I'll tell you what. Let's talk about it later.
也许我们该吃个晚餐再看一个电影
Maybe we'll have dinner and go to a movie.
可以吗
All right?
好吗
Okay?
好的
Yeah.
能进来吗
You mind?
哦  没事  进来吧
Oh... no, go ahead.
就是需要打几个电话
Just have to make some calls.
你好  帮我找一下安德鲁·莱文森
Hello, Andrew Levinson, please.
安德鲁  我是艾米丽·伯恩斯利
Andrew. Emily Bernsley.
我打电话来想跟你说一下你的软禁试点计划
I'm calling about your house arrest pilot program.
我这有一个孩子很适合
I'm representing a kid who would be perfect for it.
不  我要去其他地方工作
No. I'll go work somewhere else.
嗯嗯
Mm-hmm.
我还需要一千美金  艾比 需要重新印传单
I just need another thousand dollars, Abby, to reprint the flyers.
不  不  我很认真  艾比  我不想成为一谈笑话
No, no, I'm serious, Abby. I don't want to be the butt of a joke.
赫伯·奥罗克刚刚打电话来了  他妻子同意接回菲利普了
Herb O'Rourke just called. His wife agreed to take Philip back.
是吗
Really?
真是  好消息
So... nice news.
是  是啊  真是个好消息
Yeah. Yeah. That's good news.
好消息
Nice news.
如果我再努力一点  我能通过瑟蒙德的考试的
I can pass my classes at Thurmond... if I try harder.
我想  我会再努力一点的  伯顿
I guess... I'll have to try harder, Burton.
也许  亲爱的你需要一些基础的技巧
Well, maybe you need some basic skills, honey.
我的意思是  呃  并不是你的问题  但是如果你
I mean... uh... It's not your fault, but if you... if you had...
- 如果你有一些基础的  - 我能做到的  伯顿
- if you had the basics... - I can do it, Burton.
格里森太太  我的数学老师  说我可以参加明天的补偿考试
Mrs. Gleason, my math teacher, said I could take a make-up test tomorrow.
而且我之前学过一点
And I've studied a little bit for it.
明天吗
Tomorrow?
我准备好了
I'm ready.
我能做到的
I can do it.
什么考试
Test on what?
分数和百分数  类似于这种的
Fractions and percents. Stuff like that.
哦  是么
Oh. Huh.
给我一个百分数  然后我把它转换成分数
Give me a percentage, and I can turn it into a fraction.
就这样
Go ahead.
好的
Okay.
你能把它转换成分数吗
Can you turn this into a fraction?
算了  宝贝  你现在不需要做这些的
Well... you don't have to do this now, honey.
呃  我可以的  伯顿  我不是笨蛋
Uh, I can do it, Burton. I'm not stupid.
哦  我当然知道你不是笨蛋  我知道的  亲爱的
Oh, I know you're not stupid, honey. I know that.
走吧  咱们回家吧
Come on, let's just go home.
走啦
Come on.
快点
走啦  宝贝
Come on, honey.
你  你之前说我们要去看电影的
You-- you said we were going to the movies.
香农  别无理取闹  现在要我们回去了
Shannon, this is ridiculous. Now come on.
你说过我们要出去的
You said we were going out.
宝贝  下车  然后进屋
Honey, get out of the car and come inside.
你怎么在这  你在我家做什么
What are you doing here? What are you doing in my house?
- 嘿  - 怎么了
- Hey. - What happened?
罗伊和  一些其他人
Roy and... some other guy...
我没看见他的脸
I didn't get a look at his face...
要偷你妈妈的珠宝
trying to steal your mother's jewelry.
我追他们
I ran after 'em...
但是   他们把我推倒了
but... shoved me down...
撞到了头
hit my damn head.
现在感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
哦  有点晕  没什么大问题
Oh, dizzy. It's no big deal.
我需要你  我需要你今晚照顾一下香农
Look... I need you... I need you to take care of Shannon tonight.
哦  爸爸  我
Oh, Dad... l...
真的  看  我今晚得一直在这  有脑震荡
Really. Look, I gotta be here overnight. This is a concussion.
- 今天晚上得做检查  - 好吧
- They're gonna do these tests. - Right.
我真的很关心香农
I'm really concerned about Shannon.
好吧  她在哪
All right. Where is she?
- 她在琼尼家  - 好的
- She's over at Junie's. - Okay.
那你尽快赶过去  可以吗
So get over there as soon as you can, all right?
是的  可以  我早上再给你打电话
All right. Yeah. I'll call you in the morning.
- 好  - 好的
- Yeah. - All right.
嘿  香农  告诉我
Hey, Shannon, tell me.
罗伊是怎么知道珠宝的事的
How did Roy know about the jewelry?
你告诉他的  是吗
You told him, didn't you?
是你告诉他的
You told him.
罗伊  借了一大笔钱
Roy... borrowed a lot of money...
给我买化妆品
to buy all this makeup.
这堆化妆品
This shipment of makeup.
而且他没有检查看看颜色奇不奇怪
And he didn't check to see it was all strange colors.
他以为就是正常的颜色  但是其实是一堆卖不掉的奇怪颜色
He thought it was normal, but it was all funny colors, so he couldn't sell it.
准备好明早七点走
Be ready to leave at seven in the morning.
发生的一切我很抱歉
I'm sorry about all this.
一放学就回我家
Just be back at my house right after school.
尼克  我没有想过会发生这样的事
Nick, I didn't want any of this to happen.
你会告诉伯顿的  是吗
You're gonna tell Burton, right?
我说的这些   你会告诉他吗
What I said, you're gonna tell him?
一放学就回去我家
Just be back at my house right after school.
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
感觉怎么样了
How're you feeling?
哦  还那样吧
Oh, about the same.
是嘛  那还好吧
Yeah. Good. Good.
是香农告诉罗伊珠宝的事情的
Shannon told Roy about the jewelry.
她给他留了门
She left the door open for him.
- 尼古拉斯  - 哦  爸爸
- Nicholas... - Oh, Dad,
她会一直使你陷到这样的麻烦中
she's gonna keep dragging you into this kinda trouble.
她还是个孩子
She's just a kid.
她是一个帮助她爸爸闯入你家的孩子
She's a kid that helped her father break into your house.
她就只是一个孩子啊
She's just a kid.
这是什么情况
What is this about... really?
我的意思是  你为什么一定要有这样一个人在你的生活中呢
I mean... why do you need someone like this in your life right now?
呃  我得走了
Uh... I gotta go.
嗯
Um...
要我来接你的时候  就直接  给我打电话
Just... just call me when you... when you need me to pick you up.
伯顿
Burton.
醒醒  伯顿
Hi, Burton.
嗨  伯顿
嗨
Hi.
你现在应该在学校
You should be in school.
我知道  我就是
I know, I just...
那你怎么不在学校
Why aren't you in school?
尼克告诉你我做的事了吗
Nick told you what I did?
告诉了
Yeah.
我很抱歉  伯顿
I'm so sorry, Burton.
你为什么要做这样的事情
Why in the world would you do something like that?
罗伊说他很需要钱
Roy said he needed money.
你不知道当你做这些事情的时候  会给你带来很多麻烦吗
Don't you know when you do things like that, you get in a lot of trouble?
我知道
I know.
我对你很生气
I'm angry with you.
非常生气
Very angry.
我知道
I know.
听着  去外边等着  好吗
Listen, wait outside, okay?
一小会就好
It'll be just a moment.
别担心  亲爱的  我们很快就好
Don't worry, hon. We'll be right out.
好的
All right.
法林先生因右侧颞区头部受伤而来我们医院
Mr. Fallin comes to us with a closed-head injury to the right temporal region.
软组织肿胀  但是没有颅内出血
He experienced soft-tissue swelling but no evidence of intracranial hemorrhage.
呃  而且  通过CT扫描也没有发现任何颅骨骨折
Uh... and, uh, no skull fracture also noted on the CT Scan.
呃  马斯特先生
Ah, Mr. Master-sin.
真好笑
Now that's... that's funny.
但是我得告诉你
But I'll tell you something.
我今天出去把那些传单撕下来
I went out today to pull those flyers down.
不论到哪  我都停下来跟那的人聊天
Everywhere I went, I stopped to talk to people--
关于我的竞选和我的想法
about my campaign, about my ideas.
而且你知道吗  人们都在认真听
And you know what? People were listening.
我感觉  这次错误的印刷已经吸引了他们的注意
I mean, this whole misprint got their attention,
而且他们  他们是真的在听我说
and they... they actually listened to me.
- 你继续加油吧  - 我会的
- Good for you. - Yeah.
我当然会的
I mean... yeah.
肯定会的
Yeah.
哦  尼克  你已经不在布尔西科的案子了
Oh, Nick, you're off the Bulseco case.
- 我吗  - 艾米丽解决了
- I am? - Emily resolved it.
- 哦  是她解决的吗  - 是啊  真是不可思议
- Oh, she did? - Yeah, she's incredible.
真的是不可思议
Really incredible.
太棒了
Fantastic.
哦  你还在啊
Oh, you're still here.
露露给了我一些你的案子
Lulu gave me a couple of your cases.
- 很好啊  - 所以我有一些工作需要做
- Great. - So I have to do some work.
嗯
Hmm.
我就只是工作  而且你也可以
I'll just work... and you can, too.
抱歉  尼克
Excuse me, Nick.
很抱歉打扰到你们
Sorry to interrupt.
奥罗克太太有产后抑郁症
Mrs. O'Rourke has post-partum depression.
她
She...
今天早上她状态不太好
This morning she had kind of a break.
她要伤害菲利普  但是他光着脚跑出来了
She tried to hit Philip, and he ran outside in his bare feet.
她把门锁上了
She locked the door.
直到她的丈夫下班回来才让他进屋
Didn't let him back in till her husband came home from work.
我就只是在房间里写作业
I was just doing my homework in the family room.
然后她就开始冲我大喊
And she starts screaming at me.
菲利普的脸上  手上  还有脚上都刚接受完冻伤治疗
Philip was treated for frostbite on his face, his hands, and his feet.
奥罗克夫人现在在哪呢
Where's Mrs. O'Rourke now?
他们把她送去医院了
They took her to the hospital.
你刚刚说她怎么了  她得了什么病
What did you say about her? What does she have?
亲爱的  她生了这样一种病
She's got this thing, honey,
就是有的人怀宝宝的时候会得的病
that people sometimes get when they have a baby.
这种病会使他们行为很奇怪
It makes them act funny.
并不是她的错  只是她现在生了这样的一种病
It's not her fault. She's just kinda sick right now.
那我能回家了吗
Do I get to go home?
宝贝  我们会给你另外找一个好地方的
We'll find a good place for you, sweetheart.
法林先生
Mr. Fallin?
我们会给你找一个更好的地方的
We'll find a better place for you.
我明白  但是如果你有其他的消息
I understand, but if you learn anything else,
能不能告诉我
would you... would you let me know?
我很感激  谢谢
I appreciate it. Thank you.
感觉好点了吗
Feeling any better?
你最近有香农的消息吗
Have you heard anything from Shannon recently?
没有  我早上把她放在学校了
No. I dropped her at school this morning...
刚刚在这待了一会  之后就走了
She was here a while ago. She just disappeared.
刚才就是学校的电话
That was the school.
他们说她今天根本没去上学
They said she never showed up at all today.
什么
What?
说你早上打电话过去了
Said you called this morning
而且跟他们说她今天不舒服
and told them that she was not feeling well...
没有啊  根本没有  我没打电话  我没给学校打电话
No, that's not true. I didn't call. I didn't call the school.
爸爸  别担心  她可能跟罗伊在一起呢
Dad, don't worry. She's probably with Roy.
她可能就是
She's probably just...
你要干什么
What are you doing?
呃  你好  我是伯顿·法林
Uh, yeah, this is Burton·Fallin.
我的养女香农  是彭妮的朋友
My foster child Shannon is a... a friend of Penny's.
是的   是的
Yeah, right.
我想了解一下  她今天有没有跟香农联系过
Wondering if, uh... if she had talked to, uh, Shannon at all today.
不  不  不  我在这边等着  谢谢
No. No, no. I'll-- I'll hold. Thank you.
如果你想的话  我可以开车转一转  找找她
I can just take a drive around and look for her, if you'd like.
哪啊
Where?
- 好吧  - 什么
- Well... - Yes?
从昨天开始就没有啊
Not since yesterday.
没  没有  她不是
No, no. She wasn't...
她今天没有去学校  所以
she wasn't at school today, so...
好的  那好吧  谢谢
Okay. Well, thank you.
呃  如果你有她的任何消息  可不可以给我回个电话
Uh... would you... would you give me a call if you hear anything at all?
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
她经常去哪逛
Where does she hang out?
我不知道  商场  我真不知道
I don't know. The mall... I don't know.
好吧  我可以开着车然后
Well, I can just jump in the car and...
你好
Hello.
是的
Yes.
哦  不  不  不  我马上就到
Oh, no, no, no. I'll be right over.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
警察找到罗伊了
The police found Roy.
他说他有香农的消息
He says he has some information about Shannon.
谢谢
Thanks.
罗伊想做一个交易
Roy wants to make a deal.
来帮他找到他的亲身女儿吗
To help find his own daughter?
他想做个交易
He wants to make a deal.
- 他会请求减刑吗  - 是的
- He will plea down to a misdemeanor? - Right.
地方检察官会同意吗
And the DA's gonna go for that?
如果我同意的话  毕竟我是受害者  所以
lf I approve. I'm the victim, so...
你别同意
You're not doing that.
他会帮我找到香农
He can help me find Shannon.
你不能就这样放过这个混蛋
You can't just let this guy off.
尼古拉斯  他说他有消息
Nicholas, he says he has information.
香农离家出走是因为她对你做的事
Shannon ran away because of what she did to you.
先想想这个吧
Now think about it.
她不是丢了  爸爸  她只是离家出走
She's not missing, Dad. She ran away.
当她想再跟你要什么的时候  她自然就会回来
She will be back the moment she wants something more from you.
听着  尼克  如果你不想帮忙  那就别在这捣乱  好吗
Listen, Nick, if you don't want to help, I don't want you here. Okay?
好了  回家去吧
All right. Go home.
她和马尔科姆在一起
She's with Malcolm.
- 马尔科姆  - 那个摄影师吗
- Malcolm? - The photographer.
- 你怎么知道的  - 香农给我打电话了
- How do you know that? - Shannon called me.
她说她现在有困难
She says she was in trouble.
她  呃  她说你不想要她了
She, uh... she said you didn't want her anymore.
我从来没有说过这样的话
I never said anything like that.
我想去找她  但是我还没到马尔科姆家  他们就把我抓起来了
I tried to find her, but they picked me up before I could get to Malcolm's place.
法林先生
Mr. Fallin.
她不在这
She's not here.
什么意思
Well, what does that mean?
我们在里面找到了些别的东西  一些女人的照片
We found some things inside... pictures of women.
大多数都是成人的东西
Most of it's just your garden variety adult stuff.
但是我们也的确找到了让我们不安的东西  小孩子的照片
But we did find some photos that disturbed us-- young kids.
哦  天哪
Oh, God.
有香农的吗
Any of those Shannon?
不  没有
No. No.
先回家吧
Just go home.
有其他消息我们会再通知你
We'll call you if we hear anything.
好的
Yeah.
有其他消息你们会通知我吗
You'll... you'll call me if you hear anything?
我们会的
We'll call you.
法林先生
Mr. Fallin.
警察搜查马尔科姆的摄影棚
The police went through Malcolm's studio.
找到了很多小女孩的照片
Found a lot of pictures of young girls.
儿童色情照片  罗伊
Child pornography, Roy.
你怎么能把她单独扔给这样一个
How could you leave her alone with that kind of--
你以为我会料想到事情会发生成这样吗
You think I had any idea that was going on?
你介绍的他们
You introduced them.
我不是那个让她觉得自己是一个垃圾的人
I wasn't the one who made her feel like a piece of crap.
你现在只需要让我知道关于马尔科姆的一切
You just have to let me know everything you know about Malcolm.
我们之前一起做生意
We were in business together.
他跟我提到了这些化妆品
He told me about this shipment of makeup,
所以我们从一些人哪里借了钱
so we borrowed some money from some guys,
之后我们又还不起
and we can't pay them back.
这就是你闯进我家的原因吗
That's why you broke in my house?
我需要钱
I needed the money.
你认为他们在一起安全吗
Do you think she's safe with him?
马尔科姆不会伤害她的
Malcolm's not gonna hurt her.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
因为他有点喜欢她
'Cause he kinda likes her.
什么
What?
马尔科姆喜欢她  法林先生
Malcolm likes her, Mr. Fallin.
她才十三岁
She's thirteen years old.
也许在你的世界里  13岁还是一个孩子
Maybe in your world, thirteen's just a kid.
但是在我们的世界  我的意思是  香农的妈妈15岁时我们认识了
ln ours... I mean, Shannon's mom was fifteen when I met her.
她16岁的时候我们有了香农
She was sixteen when she had Shannon.
所以  马尔科姆需要钱  然后  卖儿童色情片
So... Malcolm needs money and... sells child pornography,
现在他跟香农单独在一起  是吧
and he's alone with Shannon, huh?
我不关心你来自于哪个世界  罗伊
I don't care what world you're from, Roy.
实在太糟糕了
This is not good.
你说你想要收养菲利普
You say you want Philip in your home.
我们只是希望能再有一次机会  法官大人  我们之前不知道
We just want another chance, Your Honor. We didn't know.
我只是希望能再有一次机会
I just want another chance.
索尔特女士  你怎么看
Ms. Solt, what's your position?
我认为已经没有给像菲利普这样的孩子提供的好地方了
I think there aren't many good placements for a kid like Philip.
这并不是最好的建议
That's not the greatest recommendation.
我只是就事论事
I'm just being realistic.
法林先生呢
Mr. Fallin?
奥罗克太太  呃  指责菲利普伤害他们的孩子
Mrs. O'Rourke, uh, accused Philip of abusing their baby,
然后她虐待菲利普
then she abused Philip.
在我们带着孩子出院之前
Before we left the hospital with the baby,
一个护士过来跟我们提到了产后抑郁症
a nurse came to talk to us, and she mentioned post-partum depression,
但是在所有的事情中
but amongst a whole list of other things.
那是我第一次听说它  那我们之前又怎么会知道
That was the first time I'd ever heard of it before, so how were we to know?
奥罗克先生  你的太太什么时候出院
Mr. O'Rourke, when is your wife due to be released?
两周之后
ln two weeks.
这有一封她医生的解释说明书
Got a letter here from her doctor explaining everything.
我只是想给她正确的药物治疗  就这样
I just want to get her medications right, that's all.
如果菲利普想回到奥罗克家  那他就可以
lf Philip wishes to return to the O'Rourkes, he can.
但是由菲利普决定
But it's up to Philip.
复印这一页  之后还有这一页
Photocopy this page and then just this page,
弄好之后  麻烦拿到我的办公室
and when you're done, if you could bring it to my office.
- 尼克  - 谢谢
- Nick. - Thanks.
- 我能跟你聊一会吗  - 当然可以
- Can I talk to you for a sec? - Sure.
是关于艾米丽的
It's about Emily Bernsley.
我  呃  今天给威廉·柯克打电话了
l, uh... called William·Kirk today,
就是跟她说她工作表现很好
just to say what a great job she was doing
也是为拖了她这么久道歉
and to apologize for keeping her so long,
然后他说他上周解雇了她
and he said that he fired her last week.
真的么  为什么啊
Really? Why?
他没说
He didn't say.
他说因为她的爸爸  事情很尴尬
He said it was awkward because of her dad and...
不管怎么说  我认为她是一个很好的律师
Anyway, I think that she's a really good lawyer.
我不知道该跟她说什么
I just don't know what I should say to her.
- 你爸爸打电话了  -是吗
- Your dad called. - He did?
说他在家
Said he's at home.
你喜欢在这吗
Do you like it here?
当然
Yeah.
- 菲利普来了  - 好的
- Philip's here. - Okay.
最近怎样
How you doing?
还好
Fine.
- 你呢  - 还好  还不错
- You? - Yeah, fine, fine.
- 好的  - 好的
- Okay.- Okay.
嘿
Hey.
法林先生
Mr. Fallin.
菲利普
Philip.
那  我们跟法官说过了  他说你自己决定
So we, uh, we spoke to the judge, and he said it's... it's up to you.
如果你想回去  那就回去
lf you want to go back home, then you can go back.
但是如果你不想  我们就给你找一个更好的
But if you don't, then we can find you a better place.
你一直说你会给我找一个更好的地方
You keep saying you'll find me a better place.
是的
Right.
但是你并不是认真的  是吗
But you don't really mean it, do you?
我记得当时奥罗克一家选择了我
I remember when the O'Rourkes chose me.
其他人都不要我
Nobody else wanted me.
我都记得
I remember that.
如果有其他人想要我  你就会同意
lf people want somebody like me, you go with them.
是吧  法林先生
Right, Mr. Fallin?
如果可以的话  我就只想回家
lf it's okay, I just want to go home.
确定吗
Sure?
确定
Sure.
拿点吧  发出去啊
Take some... hand 'em out.
我跟艾米丽聊了
So I spoke to Emily.
是吗
Yeah?
她住在家里  早上跟她爸爸一起上班
She lives at home, and she commutes in the morning with her dad,
她很担心他怎样接受这个消息
and she was afraid  how he was gonna take the news.
而且他不知道她已经被解雇了
And he doesn't know that she was fired,
所以  这就是她最近一直在这边逛的原因
so that's why she's been hanging out here all week.
我还是希望能在这边志愿服务
I'd still like to volunteer here.
哦  好啊  当然可以
Oh, yeah, of course.
我是真的喜欢你们在做的事情
I really like what you guys do.
谢谢
Thank you.
我现在得去见我爸爸了
I have to meet my dad now.
好  拜拜
Okay. See you.
拿点吧   给马斯特森投票啊
Take a few. Vote for Masterson.
你为什么不给她提供一份工作啊
Why don't you give her a job?
是啊  也许吧
Yeah. Yeah. Maybe.
好吧  之前是你说她不错的
Well, you said she's good.
嘿
Hey.
又跟那个侦探聊了
Talked to that detective again.
他说他们会尽全力的
He said they'll do the best they can.
好的
Right.
尽他们的全力
The best they can.
是我的错
It's my fault.
- 是我造成的这一切  - 不 爸爸  不怪你
- I did this. - No, Dad, no.
你没有错
You didn't.
如果明天我还收不到任何消息
Well... if I don't hear something by tomorrow...
- 她会回来的  - 哦
- She'll be back. - Oh.. .
是劳瑞·绍尔特
It's Laurie·Solt.
怎么了
Why?
我们要进行一个  她明天要跟香农聊关于领养的事
We had a... She was gonna interview Shannon for the adoption and...
- 算了  - 不  爸爸
- Well... - No, Dad.
我来跟她解释
I'll talk to her.
我来解释
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177